Register of the American Relief Administration Russian operational records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Subject File, 1921-1925
  - Agreements
    - Nansen, Fritjof (Folder 5)
    - Riga (Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Committee hearings (Folder 7)
  - Agriculture Department (Folder 8)
  - All Russian Central Executive Committee (Folder 9)
  - American Committee for Relief of Russian Children (Folder 10)
  - American Friends of Russia (Folder 11)
  - American organizations (Folder 12)
  - American Red Cross (Box 312)
    - General
      - 1921 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 389
      - 1922- (Folder 2)
      - 1923- (Folder 3)
    - Cables (Folder 4)
  - Anti-religious activities of Soviets (Folder 5)
  - Appeals
    - 1921-1922 (Folder 6)
    - 1923 (Folder 7)
  - Applications
    - A-C (Folder 8)
    - D-F (Folder 9)
    - G-I (Box 313, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 390
    - J-L (Folder 2)
    - M (Folder 3)
    - N-Q (Folder 4)
    - R-S (Folder 5)
    - T-Z (Folder 6)
  - Armenia (Folder 7)
  - Arrivals, discharges, etc. (Folder 8)
  - Artist benefits - Chauve Souris performance (Folder 9)
  - Associations, societies, etc. (Folder 10)
  - Attacks, criticisms, etc. (Box 314, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 391
  - Austria (Folder 2)
  - Automobiles (Folder 3)
  - Badura, Anna (Folder 4)
  - Bags (Folder 5)
  - Barclay, E. M. (Folder 6)
  - Barrett, Paul Sheldon (Folder 7)
  - Barringer, Thomas C. (Folder 8)
  - Bell, W. L. (Folder 9)
  - Beschorner, Gustav (Folder 10)
  - Black Sea Shipping (Folder 11)
  - Blake, Judson (Folder 12)
  - Blandy, Harold (Folder 13)
  - Bloomfield, Meyer (Folder 14)
  - Bogen, Dr. (Folder 15)
  - Boiumstrov, W. W. (Folder 16)
  - Brent, T. (Folder 17)
  - Bristol, Admiral (Folder 18)
  - Brooks, Sidney (Folder 19)
  - Brown, David A. (Folder 20)
  - Brown, Joseph (Folder 21)
  - Bulk sales (Folder 22)
  - Burland, Elmer G. (Folder 23)
  - Burns, Allen T. (Folder 24)
  - Cables (corrected) (Folder 25)
  - California (Folder 26)
  - Canada (Folder 27)
  - Canadian Red Cross (Folder 28)
  - Cantacuzene, Princess (Box 315, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 392
  - Carasso, Alexander (Folder 2)
  - Carden, G. L. (Folder 3)
  - Cargoes (Folder 4)
  - Cars (Folder 5)
  - Catholics (Folder 6)
  - Catons (Folder 7)
  - Central States Volga Relief Society (Folder 8)
  - Chadbrow, Nathan (Folder 9)
  - Chicherin (Folder 10)
  - Child feeding
    - General
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 11)
      - 1923 (Folder 12)
    - Parents' fee (Folder 13)
  - Childs, J. Rives (Folder 14)
  - China (Folder 15)
  - Chinchuk (Folder 16)
  - Christmas (Folder 17)
  - Church campaigns and appeals (Folder 18)
  - Cibrario, J. (Folder 19)
  - Clippings (Folder 20)
  - Clothing
    - General
      - 1921 (Folder 21)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 316, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 393
    - Drafts
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Children (Folder 3)
      - Continuation by A.R.A. men (Folder 4)
      - Cooperation of Textile Division of the Department of Commerce (Folder 5)
      - Forms, blanks, etc. (Folder 6)
      - Purchases - Army woolens (Folder 7)
      - Sales, statements, etc. (Folder 8)
  - Colton, E. T. (Folder 9)
  - Commission of Inquiry (Folder 10)
  - Commodities
    - General (Folder 11)
    - Availability (Folder 12)
    - Reports (Folder 13)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Folder 14)
  - Communications (Folder 15)
  - Conferences (Box 317)
    - General
      - At Mr. Hoover's house, 1923 January 23 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 394
      - Berlin - International Workmen's Famine Relief, 1922 July 9 (Folder 2)
      - Brussels (Folder 3)
      - Geneva (Folder 4)
      - Moscow (Folder 5)
      - Paris (Folder 6)
    - Minutes (Folder 7)
  - Conferences and meetings other than of Purchasing Commission (Folder 8)
  - Confidential letters (Folder 9)
  - Congressional appropriation (Folder 10)
  - Constantinople (Folder 11)
  - Coolidge, Calvin (Folder 12)
  - Cooperation of relief organizations (Folder 13)
  - Corcoran, William C. (Folder 14)
  - Corn for Russia (Folder 15)
  - Corn grits (Box 318, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 395
  - Credits
    - Against Congressional appropriation (Folder 2)
    - Against Soviet gold (Folder 3)
    - Foreign (Folder 4)
  - Crimea (Folder 5)
  - Criticisms (Folder 6)
  - Crops (Folder 7)
  - Czechoslovakia (Folder 8)
  - Daley, E. L. (Folder 9)
  - Damaged cargoes (Folder 10)
  - Dates
    - Arrivals, deliveries, etc. (Folder 11)
    - Shipments (Folder 12)
    - Termination and follow-up work (Folder 13)
  - Davenport, Walter P. (Folder 14)
  - Day, Rush O. (Folder 15)
  - Dear, William R. (Folder 16)
  - Demobilization (Folder 17)
  - Deportation of Russians (Folder 18)
  - Dickinson, Thomas H. (Folder 19)
  - Difficulties (Folder 20)
  - Dinner of A.R.A. (Folder 21)
  - Dixon, Frank (Folder 22)
  - Donations (Folder 23)
  - Dulles, Allen (Folder 24)
  - Durand, E. D. (Folder 25)
  - Duranty, Walter (Box 319, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 396
  - Easley, Ralph (Folder 2)
  - Egan, Eleanor (Folder 3)
  - Eisenstadt, William (Folder 4)
  - Ellingston, John
    - General (Folder 5)
    - "The Bubble of Russian Business,", 1924 (Folder 6)
    - Letters to H. H. Fisher, 1922-1923 (Folder 7)
  - Eurelcon sales (Folder 8)
  - European Relief Council
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Meeting (Folder 10)
  - Evannikov, Cozma (Folder 11)
  - Exports of grain by Soviets (Folder 12)
  - Famine of, 1925 (Folder 13)
  - Faxon, R. H. (Folder 14)
  - Federal Society for Russian Relief (Folder 15)
  - Federated General Relief Committee (Folder 16)
  - Files and records of the A.R.A. (Folder 17)
  - Finances
    - General
      - 1922- (Folder 18)
      - 1923- (Box 320, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 397
    - Accounts in Moscow (Folder 2)
    - Liquidation (Folder 3)
  - Flag (Folder 4)
  - Fleming, Harold M. (Folder 5)
  - Flour (Folder 6)
  - Food
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Drafts
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Cables
        - 1921 (Folder 9)
        - 1922 January->February (Folder 10)
        - 1922 March-April (Folder 11)
        - 1922 May-August (Folder 12)
        - 1922 September-1923 (Folder 13)
      - Continuation by A.R.A. men (Folder 14)
      - Far East (Folder 15)
    - Drafts, prices (Box 321, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 398
    - Drafts, sales, etc., 1922 September-1923 (Folder 2)
    - Sales
      - 1921 November-1922 January (Folder 3)
      - 1921 November-1922 April (Folder 4)
      - June, 1922 May-June (Folder 5)
      - 1922 July-August (Folder 6)
    - Sales, statements, etc. (Folder 7)
    - Stocks (Folder 8)
  - Food Administration reunion (Folder 9)
  - Foreign press
    - 1921 (Folder 10)
    - 1922 January-July (Box 322, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 399
    - 1922 August-1923 September (Folder 2)
  - Form and circular letters (Folder 3)
  - Fourcar, Frederic H. (Folder 4)
  - France
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Foreign relations - Russia, 1923 February 8 (Folder 6)
  - Freeman, The (Folder 7)
  - Friends Service Committee
    - 1921 (Folder 8)
    - 1922 January-March (Folder 9)
    - 1922 April-1923 (Folder 10)
  - Friends of Soviet Russia (Folder 11)
  - Friends Service Committee. Cables (Folder 12)
  - Funds (Folder 13)
  - Gardner, Nellie E. (Folder 14)
  - Garner, Ruth (Folder 15)
  - Garner, William C. (Box 323, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 400
  - Germany (Folder 2)
  - Gest, Marris (Folder 3)
  - Gibbs, Philip, Sir (Folder 4)
  - Gilchrist, Harry L. (Folder 5)
  - Golder, Frank A.
    - 1921 January-1922 July (Folder 6)
    - 1922 August (Folder 7)
    - 1922 September-December (Folder 8)
    - 1923 January-March (Folder 9)
    - 1923 April-May (Folder 10)
    - 1923 June (Folder 11)
  - Goodrich, James P. (Folder 12)
  - Gorky, Maksim (Folder 13)
  - Gottlieb, Rose (Folder 14)
  - Grain (Box 324)
    - Production (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 401
    - Statistics (Folder 2)
  - Great Britain (Folder 3)
  - Gregg, John P. (Folder 4)
  - Grove, W. R. (Folder 5)
  - Guaranty Trust Company (Folder 6)
  - Haines, Anna J. (Folder 7)
  - Hall, Francis (Folder 8)
  - Hamburg (Folder 9)
  - Hapgood, Norman (Folder 10)
  - Harrison, Marguerite E. (Folder 11)
  - Herter, Christian A. (Folder 12)
  - Herz, Ralph (Folder 13)
  - Hibbard, C. V. (Folder 14)
  - Hibben, Paxton
    - General
      - 1922- (Folder 15)
      - 1923- (Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 17)
    - New York file (Folder 18)
  - Hiebert, P. C. (Folder 19)
  - Historical Department (Folder 20)
  - History and policy (Box 325)
    - 1921 July-1922 May (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 402
    - 1922 June (Folder 2)
  - Hofstra, Piet Hein (Folder 3)
  - Hoover, Herbert (Folder 4)
  - Horses (Folder 5)
  - House of Representatives
    - A-F (Folder 6)
    - G-L (Folder 7)
    - M-Z (Folder 8)
  - Hungary (Folder 9)
  - Hutchinson, Lincoln
    - 1921 October-1922 December (Folder 10)
    - 1923 January-May (Box 326, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 403
    - 1923 June- (Folder 2)
  - Hutchinson, Woods (Folder 3)
  - Hynes, John E. (Folder 4)
  - Ice conditions (Folder 5)
  - Insurance
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Fund (Folder 7)
  - Intellectuals (Folder 8)
  - International Red Cross (Folder 9)
  - Jewish campaign and appeals - American Jewish Relief Committee (Box 327, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 404
  - Jews (Folder 2)
  - Joint Distribution Committee
    - General
      - 1921 January-1922 May (Folder 3)
      - Includes report of, 1922 June. 1927 (Folder 4)
    - Cables
      - 1921 January-1922 July (Folder 5)
      - 1922 August (Folder 6)
  - Justice Department (Folder 7)
  - Kalinin, M. I. (Folder 8)
  - Kamenev, Lev (Folder 9)
  - Karelians (Folder 10)
  - Kellogg, Vernon (Folder 11)
  - Krasin (Folder 12)
  - Labor Department (Folder 13)
  - La Follette, Robert M. (Folder 14)
  - Lake Pray (Box 328, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 405
  - Lander, R. (Folder 2)
  - Lange, J. H. (Folder 3)
  - Larsen, Lauritz (Folder 4)
  - La Salle, J. F. (Folder 5)
  - Latvia (Folder 6)
  - Leaflets (Folder 7)
  - League of Nations (Folder 8)
  - Legislature - Acts, laws, etc. (Folder 9)
  - Lehrs, John (Folder 10)
  - Lenin, V. I. (Folder 11)
  - Lists (Folder 12)
  - Literature (Folder 13)
  - Loeb, Marris J. (Folder 14)
  - Lonergan, Thomas C. (Box 329, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 406
  - Lvov, Prince
    - 1921-1923 (Folder 2)
    - 1924-1925 (Folder 3)
  - MacLean, H. C. (Folder 4)
  - Maitland, John I. (Folder 5)
  - Mandel, S. M., Mrs. (Folder 6)
  - Maps (Folder 7)
  - Marsh, Benjamin C. (Folder 8)
  - Mathews, Major (Folder 9)
  - Mayer, Raymond C. (Folder 10)
  - Mead, Norah (Folder 11)
  - Medical personnel in Russia (Folder 12)
  - Medical supplies
    - General
      - 1921 January-1922 March (Folder 13)
      - 1922 December-1924 (Box 330, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 407
    - Cables (Folder 2)
    - Liquors, alcohol, narcotics, etc. (Folder 3)
    - Reports, lists, statements, etc.
      - General
        - 1921 January-1922 February (Folder 4)
        - 1923, 1922 March-1923 (Folder 5)
      - Report to president (Folder 6)
  - Milk (Folder 7)
  - Mimeographed reports and extracts (Box 331, Folder 1-3)
    Available on microfilm reel 408
  - Mimeographed reports and extracts (Box 332, Folder 1-2)
    Available on microfilm reel 409
  - Minnesota Russian Relief Committee (Folder 3)
  - Money remittances (Folder 4)
  - Moorehead, Dr. (Folder 5)
  - Motion pictures (Folder 6)
  - Mulford, J. Bentley (Folder 7)
  - Murphy, Farmer (Folder 8)
  - Musa, A. B. (Folder 9)
  - Nansen, Fridtjof (Folder 10)
  - Nation, The (Folder 11)
  - National Civic Federation (Folder 12)
  - National Information Bureau (Folder 13)
  - Navy Department (Box 333)
    - General (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 410
    - Destroyers in the Black Sea (Folder 2)
  - Near East Emergency Fund
    - General (Folder 3)
    - American Red Cross (Folder 4)
    - Cables (Folder 5)
    - Minutes (Folder 6)
  - Near East Relief
    - 1921 (Folder 7)
    - 1922 January-March (Folder 8)
    - 1922 April-December (Folder 9)
    - 1923 (Folder 10)
    - 1924-1925 (Folder 11)
  - Needs
    - General, 1922-1923 (Folder 12)
    - Results (Folder 13)
  - News record (Folder 14)
  - Newspaper and other publications (Box 334, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 411
  - Northwest Russia (General IUdenich), 1919 (Folder 2)
  - Ostrova, Mary (Folder 3)
  - Passports
    - 1921 (Folder 4)
    - 1922 (Folder 5)
  - Passports and miscellaneous
    - A-K (Folder 6)
    - L-Z (Folder 7)
  - Periodicals (Folder 8)
  - Personnel (Box 335)
    - General
      - Individuals
        - A-I (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 412
        - J-Z (Folder 2)
      - Letters of appreciation to (Folder 3)
      - Lists (Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1921 (Folder 5)
        - 1922 (Folder 6)
        - 1923 (Folder 7)
    - Baker, George B. (Box 336)
      - 1921-1922 March (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 413
      - 1922 April (Folder 2)
    - Barnes, Julius H. (Folder 3)
    - Beeuwkes, Henry (Folder 4)
    - Brown, Gordon (Folder 5)
    - Brown, Walter Lyman
      - 1921- (Folder 6)
      - 1922- (Folder 7)
      - 1923- (Folder 8)
    - Coolidge, A. C. (Folder 9)
    - Dailey, Arthur T. (Folder 10)
    - Fisher, H. H.
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 11)
      - 1923- (Box 337, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 414
    - Flesh, Edward M.
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 2)
    - Galpin, Perrin C.
      - General
        - 1921 January-1922 February (Folder 4)
        - 1922 March (Folder 5)
      - Enclosures
        - 1921 (Folder 6)
        - 1922 January-March (Folder 7)
        - 1922 April-June (Box 338, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 415
        - 1922 July-August (Folder 2)
        - 1922 September-November (Folder 3)
        - 1922 December-1923 January (Folder 4)
        - 1923 February-March (Folder 5)
        - 1923 April-May (Folder 6)
        - 1923 June-July (Folder 7)
    - Goodrich, James P. (Box 339)
      - 1921 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 416
      - 1922 January-May (Folder 2)
      - 1922 June (Folder 3)
    - Haskell, William N.
      - General
        - 1921 (Folder 4)
        - 1922 January-August (Box 340, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 417
        - 1922 September-December (Folder 2)
        - 1923- (Folder 3)
      - Greece (Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Robert A. (Folder 5)
    - Krueger, J. W. (Folder 6)
    - Livingston, Don (Folder 7)
    - Myers, Walker J. (Folder 8)
    - Page, Frank
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 9)
      - 1923- (Folder 10)
    - Poland, William B. (Box 341, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 418
    - Quinn, C. J. C. (Folder 2)
    - Rickard, Edgar
      - 1921 January-1922 April (Folder 3)
      - 1922 May (Folder 4)
    - Sawtelle, R. H. (Folder 5)
    - Wilkinson, Lupton A. (Folder 6)
  - Petschenko, Mme Lamprecht de (Folder 7-9)
  - Pirquet, Dr. (Folder 10)
  - Polakov, Walter N. (Folder 11)
  - Poland (Folder 12)
  - Polanska, Zenaide (Box 342, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 419
  - Postnickov, A. S. (Folder 2)
  - Post Office Department (Folder 3)
  - Press
    - Privileges (Folder 5)
    - Releases (Folder 6)
  - Price, F. J. (Folder 7)
  - Prices, rates, etc. (Folder 8)
  - Prisoners
    - 1921 (Folder 9)
    - 1922 (Folder 10)
  - Program and policy
    - 1921 (Folder 11)
    - 1922 January-March (Folder 12)
    - 1922 April-December (Box 343, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 420
    - 1923 (Folder 2)
  - Publicity
    - General
      - 1921 January-1922 May (Folder 3)
      - 1922 June (Folder 4)
    - Cable book (Folder 5)
    - Clippings (Folder 6)
  - Purchases
    - General
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 7)
      - 1923 (Folder 8)
    - Flour and corn grits, 1921-1923 (Folder 9)
  - Purchasing Commission
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Minutes (Box 344, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 421
    - Reports
      - To the President (Folder 2)
      - To the Secretary of Treasury (Folder 3)
  - Railway employees (Folder 4)
  - Rascality, dishonesty, inefficiency in connection with relief work (Folder 5)
  - Rations (Folder 6)
  - Reconstruction work (Folder 7)
  - Redfield, William C. (Folder 8)
  - Repatriation
    - 1921 (Folder 9)
    - 1922 (Folder 10)
  - Replacement (Folder 11)
  - Reports
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Fisher, H. H., book on Russia (Folder 13)
    - Personnel
      - A-C (Folder 14)
      - D-G (Box 345, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 422
      - Golder, Frank A. (Folder 2)
      - H-M (Folder 3)
      - Hutchinson, Lincoln (Folder 4)
      - Mitchell, Mowatt (Folder 5)
      - N-Z (Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 7)
    - To the President, 10, 1922 July (Folder 8)
  - Reports, cables, etc. (Folder 9)
  - Reports, notes, memoranda, etc.
    - 1921 August-October (Folder 10)
    - 1921 November-December (Folder 11)
    - 1922 January-March (Folder 12)
    - 1922 April-December (Box 346, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 423
    - 1923- (Folder 2)
  - Reports, statements, etc.
    - General (Folder 3)
    - A.R.A. bulletins (Folder 4)
    - Crops (Folder 5)
    - Purchases, shipments, arrivals, discharges, etc. (Folder 6-7)
  - Repp, George (Box 347, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 424
  - Requisitions (Folder 2)
  - Return cargoes (Folder 3)
  - Rice (Folder 4)
  - Richards, George R. (Folder 5)
  - Richey, Lawrence (Folder 6)
  - Ricker, A. S. (Folder 7)
  - Riga (Folder 8)
  - Ringland, Arthur C. (Folder 9)
  - Risner, Henry C. (Folder 10)
  - Robertson, Benjamin, Sir (Folder 11)
  - Rochester community chest (Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Folder 13)
  - Romania (Folder 14)
  - Rosen, Dr. (Folder 15)
  - Rosenberg, James N. (Folder 16)
  - Rosenfelt, Henry H. (Folder 17)
  - Rothschiller, Jacob (Folder 18)
  - Ruhl, Arthur (Folder 19)
  - Russian Famine Fund (Folder 20)
  - Russian Information Bureau (Folder 21)
  - Russian Reconstruction Farms (Folder 22)
  - Russian Red Cross (Folder 23)
  - Russian Students Fund (Folder 24)
  - Russian Union Record (Box 348)
    - 1922 February-July (Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 425
    - 1922 August-December (Folder 2)
    - 1923 January-March (Folder 3)
    - 1923 April-June (Folder 4)
  - Rye (Box 349, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 426
  - Ryerson, Emily B. (Folder 2)
  - Sakowitz (Folder 3)
  - Sales (Folder 4)
  - Samara (Folder 5)
  - Save the Children Fund (Folder 6)
  - Sawitt, Mrs. (Folder 7)
  - Scientists (Folder 8)
  - Seeds for planting (Folder 9)
  - Senate
    - A-G (Folder 10)
    - Brookhart, S. W. (Folder 11)
    - France, Joseph I. (Folder 12)
    - Frelinghuysen, J. E. (Folder 13)
    - H-L (Folder 14)
    - M-Z (Folder 15)
    - McNary, Charles L. (Folder 16)
    - Norris, G. W. (Folder 17)
    - Pepper, George W. (Folder 18)
    - Pomerene, Atlee (Folder 19)
  - Shafroth, William C.
    - General (Folder 20)
    - "The New Russia" (Folder 21)
  - Sheehan, James A. (Box 350, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 427
  - Sheild, Philip B. (Folder 2)
  - Sherman, Edwin (Folder 3)
  - Shipments
    - General (Folder 4)
    - South Russia (Folder 5)
  - Shipping
    - Cables
      - 1921 January-1922 February (Folder 6)
      - 1922 March-1923 (Folder 7)
    - Foreign bottoms (Folder 8)
    - P.N. Grey Company (Folder 9)
    - Rates (Folder 10)
    - Tickets (Folder 11)
  - Shipping and receiving ports (Folder 12)
  - Ships
    - A-C (Folder 13)
    - D-E (Box 351, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 428
    - F-M (Folder 2)
    - N-R (Folder 3)
    - S-U (Folder 4)
    - W-Z (Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 6)
  - Shoes (Folder 7)
  - Siberia (Folder 8)
  - Simbirsk (Folder 9)
  - Situation of Russian relief (Folder 10)
  - Slobodsky (Folder 11)
  - Smith, Barry (Folder 12)
  - Smith, Catherine (Folder 13)
  - Smuggling (Folder 14)
  - Soap (Folder 15)
  - Sorieri, Luigi (Folder 16)
  - Sosedova, Mary Platanovna (Folder 17)
  - Soup kitchens (Folder 18)
  - Soviet Union
    - General
      - 1921 (Folder 19)
      - 1922 (Folder 20)
      - 1923 (Folder 21)
    - Attitude toward A.R.A. (Box 352, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 429
    - Bolshevism, Reds, propaganda, etc. (Folder 2)
    - Embassy (United States) (Folder 3)
    - Gold
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Cables (Folder 5)
      - Purchases (Folder 6)
    - Recognition (Folder 7)
    - Sympathizers (Folder 8)
  - Spargo, John (Folder 9)
  - Speaks, John C. (Folder 10)
  - Special cases (Folder 11)
  - State Department
    - 1921 (Folder 12)
    - 1922 January-April (Folder 13)
    - 1922 May-July (Box 353, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 430
    - 1922 August-December (Folder 2)
    - 1923 (Folder 3)
  - Statistics of pre-war food production (Folder 4)
  - Stocks (Folder 5)
  - Strauss, Lewis (Folder 6)
  - Student feeding (Folder 7)
  - Sugar (Folder 8)
  - Suggestions (Folder 9)
  - Summers, Natalia (Folder 10)
  - Sveshnikov, Dr. (Folder 11)
  - Sweden (Folder 12)
  - Taxes (Folder 13)
  - Tractors (Folder 14)
  - Transcaucasia (Folder 15)
  - Transportation (Folder 16)
  - Traynham, Floyd (Folder 17)
  - Treasury Department (Folder 18)
  - Trotsky, Leon (Folder 19)
  - Trucks (Folder 20)
  - Turkey (Folder 21)
  - U.S. Grain Corporation (Folder 22)
  - Ughet, Serge (Box 354, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 431
  - Ukraine
    - 1921 January-1922 April (Folder 2)
    - 1922 May-1923 (Folder 3)
  - United States. Consul General (Moscow) (Folder 4)
  - United States Shipping Board Emergency Fleet Corporation (Folder 5)
  - Urquhart, Leslie (Folder 6)
  - Vegetables (Folder 7)
  - Volovsky, Gidel (Folder 8)
  - Vrangel, Baroness (Folder 9)
  - Wahren, I. (Folder 10)
  - Walker, Herschel C. (Folder 11)
  - Wallis, J. H. (Folder 12)
  - War Department
    - General (Folder 13)
    - Army officers and A.R.A. (Folder 14)
    - Supplies (Folder 15)
    - Surplus
      - Clothing (Folder 16)
      - Medical supplies (Folder 17)
  - Wardwell, Allen (Folder 18)
  - Warehouses (Folder 19)
  - Watinsen, Hattie (Folder 20)
  - Webb, George (Folder 21)
  - Weekly circular letters from Moscow (Box 355, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 432
  - Wekesser, H. P. (Folder 2)
  - Wheat (Folder 3)
  - Whiting, N. S. (Folder 4)
  - Willoughby, Charles M. (Folder 5)
  - Wilson, Randolf (Folder 6)
  - Wiren, Alexis R. (Folder 7)
  - Zavalishin (Folder 8)
  - Zemstvo and town relief (Folder 9)
- Washington Office, Telegrams, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 432-444
  Telegrams sent and received by the Washington office of the A.R.A., arranged by subseries (telegrams received and telegrams sent) and by geographic area thereunder.
  - General (Box 355)
    - Publicity
      - Incoming (Folder 10)
      - Outgoing (Folder 11)
    - State Department (Folder 12)
  - Incoming (Box 356)
    - General
      - Conloyork (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 433
      - Hamloyork (Folder 2)
      - Hamyork (Folder 3)
      - Mosloyork (Folder 4)
      - Rigyork (Folder 5)
      - Venloyork (Folder 6)
      - Warloyork (Folder 7)
    - London to New York
      - 1921 July-December (Folder 8)
        Available on microfilm reel 433A
      - 1922 January (Folder 9)
      - 1922 February (Box 357, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 434
      - 1922 March (Folder 2)
      - 1922 April (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 435
      - 1922 May-June (Folder 4)
      - 1922 July-September (Box 358, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 436
      - 1922 October-December (Folder 2)
      - 1923 January (Folder 3)